tornadovideos.net 2014-07-01

# TornadoVideos.Net | Privacy Policy

TornadoVideos.net is a trade name of Weather Fusion LLC. TornadoVideos.net knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting TornadoVideos.net, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

The information we learn from visitors helps us to continually improve TornadoVideos.net. Here are the types of information we gather:   
****

_Information You Give Us:_

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests and communicating with you. ****

_Automatic Information:_

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Also, we use Google AdSense as a third-party vendor to display ads on our site. These advertisements use the DART cookie to serve ads based on your visits to our site and other internet websites. To opt out of the DART cookie, please visit Google's ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We respect your privacy and appreciate your support. At no time do we share your information with any third party unless absolutely neccessary.

For security purposes TornadoVideos.net sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website.

Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu. Or you can email us at: [admin@tornadovideos.net](mailto:%20admin@twisterdata.com).
